https://www.alltimefashions.com/privacy-policy/

0
No products in the cart.
Contact
Search:
Privacy policy
Home > Privacy policy
We, at AllTimeFashions.com know how important it is to protect your confidential information and have taken all possible measures to ensure the protection of your information.The personal information that we collect may include your address, name, email address and phone number. AllTimeFashions.com (“the site”) does not sell, rent or disclose any identifiable detail at the personal level regarding its consumers to any 3rd party.We may make use of your personal details for different purposes like fulfilling request for products, information or services, administering contests or promotions, providing customer services, providing new products & services & improving the efficiency of our website or making strategies as well as adapting our offers to your choices.We may also make use of anonymous, non-personal data to complete tracking information reports concerning the site user demographics, website purchases and website traffic patterns & after that provide those reports to advertisers & others. None of the tracking details in the reports can be linked to the identities or other confidential info of the individual user. We may also connect tracking data with personal details voluntarily provided by the site users. Once such a connection in made, all of the linked details is treated as individual information & will be used as well as disclosed only in line with this policy.Like many other sites, we automatically gather certain non-personal details regarding the users that do not identify you. for instance we collect IP address of your system, internet service provider & the date and time when you accessed the site, the internet address of the site from where you linked to our site, the operating system, the section of the website and the content your download from the site.The non-personal information that we gather is used for website system administration purposes as well as to improve our site.
Implied AuthorityWe will never put your personal details up for sale, however we may share your details with third parties on your behalf, for instance to a shipment services, a product repair service etc. as permitted or needed by law.
In other cases we may use your personal details to advise you of our services or products that may be of significance to you. You can at all times decline to have your information used for such purpose. For instance, when you subscribe to our mails or newsletter, we consider that you provided us your permission to send you promotional details. You can always opt out or unsubscribe from the service. You may access the unsubscribe option from any of our emails sent to you.
This privacy policy is subject to change over time. For more details on privacy you can contact our customer service.
Customer CommunicationWe use your information to communicate changes to our site that may affect your account; we communicate the status of your orders as well as sending you promotions via email.
Third PartiesWe will not disclose your personal information to third parties. We use your personal information for our own purposes only. We do share aggregate information that does not identify you personally with advertisers, business partners, sponsors, and other third parties.
PaymentsFor all credit/debit card purchasers, your credit card number and other relevant billing information will be passed only as needed to third parties responsible for administering and completing the required transaction.
The AllTimeFashions.com style team sources the latest in fashion from around the world at prices that make it possible to be glamourous every day. Our buyers focus on high quality at great prices so you look good.
Useful linksHome
About Us
Privacy policy
Terms & Condition
Shipping & Return Policy
Contact Details
We Accept
Copyright 2019 AllTimeFashions.com
